Guide to the Board of Permanent Officers, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Board of Permanent Officers, Yale College, records
1871-1972
RU 542
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
The records consist of minutes, reports, and memoranda documenting the activities and operations of the Yale College Board of Permanent Officers. Also included are materials on faculty appointments for Yale College and the graduate schools.
Yale College (1887- )
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-C (YRG 9-C), Records of Yale College officers and faculty.
Existence and Location of Copies
Minutes of meetings (1871-1956) are available on microfilm (442 frames on 1 reel, 35mm) from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM216.
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, reports, and memoranda documenting the activities and operations of the Yale College Board of Permanent Officers. Also included are materials on faculty appointments for Yale College and the graduate schools.
Conditions Governing Access
Minutes of meetings (1871-1956) are available on microfilm. Patrons must use FILM HM 216 instead of the originals.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Faculty; Yale College (1887- ); Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Employees; Yale University -- Faculty
- Records of the Board of Permanent Officers, Yale College, 1910-1972; Accession 1978-A-010
  Conditions Governing Access
  Materials in Box 2, Folder 5 are restricted until Jan 1, 2048 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
  - Minute book, 1923-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Reports and papers, 1910-1921 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1920-1937 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Procedures: minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Faculty appointments: Yale College and the Graduate Schools, 1962-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Restricted until Jan 1, 2048.
- Minutes of meetings, circa 1871-1956; Accession 19ND-A-089
  Minutes of meetings are available on microfilm. Patrons must use FILM HM 216 instead of the originals.
  - Volume 1, 1871-1910 (Box 1, Reel 1U)
  - Volume 2, 1910-1923 (Box 1, Reel 1U)
  - Volume 3, 1923-1956 (Box 1, Reel 1U)